I was always wondering why
мне было всегда интересно почему же
Ukraine banned our Russian languages
Украина запрещала наши русские языки
your Russian languages ​​interesting because
ваши русские языки интересно потому что
Russian is not your language
русский - это не ваш язык
Russian is not our
русский не наш
language damn I would like to hear from you well
язык блин мне бы хотелось от вас
why is that well Slavic
услышать ну почему это ну славянские
languages ​​came from Kyiv Russian Ukrainian
языки пошли с Киева русский украинский
Belarusian in Kyiv they were invented by
белорусский в Киеве были придуманы ещё
Prince
князем
Vladimir hello
Владимиром здравствуйте
hello where are you from
здравствуйте вы откуда
I am from Khabarovsk it's cool you have it in
я с Хабаровск прикольно у вас это в
Greek or in Slavic style shirt
греческом или в славянском стиле рубаха
yes it is Yes it's just wallpaper not a shirt
да это Да это просто обои не рубаха
and Versace
а Версачи
got it Greek Versace got it
понял греческий Версачи понял
and what do you communicate with
а чем общаетесь
yes I just kind of got into chat roulette
да я просто как бы вот в чат рулетку
today I decided to just well
попал вот сегодня вот решил просто ну
like well look got it
как бы ну посмотреть
and more and
понял ещё и
more what did you watch
ещё что посмотрели
interesting people quarrel among themselves
интересно люди между собой ссорятся
cool and why should we quarrel we are just
прикольно а что нам ссориться мы же
ordinary people well
простые люди
like yeah
ну как бы да
look I'm all choosing some
смотрите я вот вот все выбирают какие-то
countries they
вот страны они между собой
communicate with each other I'm wondering I didn't choose anyone
общаются я интересно я никого не выбирал
I was just interested in communicating with
мне просто было интересно пообщаться со
everyone but they all somehow
всеми но они вот все какие-то
perceive everything with hostility straight why
воспринимают все в штыки прямо почему
let's let's try without bayonets
давайте давайте попробуем без штыков
let's chat well
пообщаться
I'd be happy to let's what do you think
ну я с радостью давайте как вы считаете
why Russia attacked Ukraine
почему Россия напала на Украину
damn you ask such direct questions yes
блин вы такие прямые вопросы задаёте да
direct and what what to be embarrassed
прямые а что что стесняться
well I don't know it seems like you have a direct question
ну не знаю вроде бы у вас прямой вопрос
but I would also like to ask my direct question
но я хотел бы тоже свой прямой вопрос
so answer mine and then
задать так ответьте на мой и дальше
ask yours well everything is direct
задавайте свой ну всё по-прямому
honestly
по-честному
I don't think that it attacked Ukraine I
я не считаю что она напала на Украину
understand why well at
понял а почему
least because look I was
ну хотя бы потому вот смотрите мне было
always interested in why Ukraine
всегда интересно почему же Украина
banned our Russian languages
запрещала наши русские языки
your Russian languages ​​I wonder because
ваши русские языки интересно потому что
Russian is not your language
русский - это не ваш язык
Russian is not our
русский не наш
language damn I would like to hear from you
язык блин мне бы хотелось от вас
well Slavic languages ​​came from Kyiv
ну славянские языки пошли с Киева
Russian Ukrainian Belarusian in Kyiv
русский украинский белорусский в Киеве
were invented by Prince Vladimir and that's
были придуманы ещё князем Владимиром и
all show me show me so that uh
всё покажи покажи мне покажи мне чтоб ээ
in you in Russia yes uh 1,000 years ago there was a
у вас в России да ээ 1.000 лет назад был
Russian language show me some
там русский язык покажи какие-то
writings in Russian everything came from Kyiv
письмена на русском языке всё с Киева
you immediately start to burden me well
пришло вы меня сразу начинаете нагружать
I'm a historian I'm a historian just
ну я историк я историк просто
oh cool by the way look our grandfathers
ой классно кстати смотрите деды нам
constantly tell us yes that we are
постоянно рассказывают да что мы
brotherly people  no no no that's not it look
братские народ ненене не то смотри
where writing came from came to
откуда письменность пришло пришло в
Russia you
Россию
're starting to delve deeper well you didn't live at
начинаете углубляться ну вы же не жили в
that time well look the
то время ну из Киева смотри в Киев
Bulgarians brought writing to Kiev from Kiev yes the
принесли письменность болгары да
followers of Cyril and Methodius how
последователи Кирилла и Мефоди что как я
can I address you and Andrei
могу к вам обращаться а Андрей
Vasilyevich
Васильевич
Andrei Vasilyevich like look uh
андрей Васильевич как вот смотрите ээ
look our grandfathers lived my
смотрите жили же у нас деды у меня вот
grandfather also
дед тоже войну
fought in the war well he fought in the war yes he did so
воевал ну он воевал войну да он так так
and my grandfather fought in the war yes and
и у меня воевал в войну так да а вы
now you're attacking us because
теперь нападаете на нас потому
Why
что Почему
and in the sense they in the sense who is attacking
а в смысле они в смысле кто нападает на
you you Russians wait
вас вы россияне подождите во-первых
firstly firstly Andrei Vasilyevich I wanted to
во-первых Андрей Васильевич я хотел у
ask you who is attacking you
вас поинтересоваться кто на вас нападает
and secondly who are we and who are we I wanted to talk
и во-вторых кто мы и кто мы я вот хотел
about this
вот об этом
yes look I'm explaining wait give it out
да смотри объясняю подождите выдате
look who came up with it you Well wait
смотрите кто придумал вы Ну подождите
wait you're a historian I'm a simple Andrei
подождите вы историк я простой андрей
Vasilyevich well please don't interrupt
Васильевич ну пожалуйста не перебивайте
come on come on in simple I'm a simple person
давай давай во простой я простой человек
if you want I'll give you the floor speak up
если хотите я вам дам слово выскажитесь
in the sense yes the floor you  now you ask a
в смысле да слово ты сейчас задашь
question and I'll tell you I'll answer everything
вопрос и я тебе расскажу отвечу всё
come on no question no question Andrey
давай не вопрос не вопрос андрей
Vasilyevich look I've always been
Васильевич смотрите меня вот всегда
interested look I've lived my whole life
интересовало смотрите вот я всю жизнь
yes look I'm already 45 years old I've
жил да смотрите мне уже 45 лет я всю
lived my whole life and I knew that we are fraternal
жизнь жил и вот знал что мы братские
peoples I was wrong
народы я ошибался
yes that means look uh there was such a
да значит смотрите ээ тут была такая
problem well what uh it was you know we are
проблема ну что ээ было вот вы знаете мы
all brothers Slavs Ukrainians Belarusians
все братья славяне украинцы белорусы
Poles Serbs Croats and all of us like well
поляки сербы хорваты и все мы как бы ну
this is together Estonians here was the Soviet Union
это вместе эстонс вот был Советский Союз
15 Slavic
15 славянских
wait 15 Slavic republics Estonia
подожди 15 славянских республик эстония
Latvia Lithuania Ukraine Belarus Kazakhstan
Латвия Литва Украина Беларусь Казахстан
we are all brothers Slavs were all together
все мы братья славяне были все вместе
against Hitler all our grandfathers
против Гитлера воевали все наши деды
Slavs fought and now it turned out this way because
славяне и теперь так получилось потому
your Yeltsin and Gorbachev took and
ваш Ельцин и Горбачёв да взяли и
destroyed the Soviet Union because in
развалили Советский Союз потому что в
ninety-first year if because they
девяносто первом году если потому что
sold out to the Americans for a bun for what
продались американцам за булочку за что
in Moscow why they opened the first McDonald's
в Москве почему открыли McDonald's
in the Soviet Union and everything since then and it all
первый в Советском Союзе и всё с тех пор
started people tried these
и понеслось люди попробовали этих
buns on  some kind of pricked and everyone
булочек на наколотых каких-то да и всё
started listening to the voice of America
начали слушать голос Америки
yes why in Moscow in Moscow in the Soviet
да почему в Москве в Москве в Советском
Union they made the first McDonald's on
Союзе сделали первый Макдональдс на
Red Square and there was a line pozvo the
Красной площади и очередь стояла подзор
Americans showed how poor poor
американцы показывали какие нищие бедные
hungry Russians were and soviet yes why they
голодные россияне и совескою да что
stood in line for a day for a bun at
стояли день в очередь за булочкой в
McDonald's America laughed then Yeltsin
McDonald's америка смеялась потом Ельцин
your Igor Bachev agents of the West flew to
ваш Игорь Бачёв агенты Запада полетели в
America they were given jeans there they were given gum
Америку им там дали джинсы дали жвачку
normal food they came and
еду нормальную дали они приехали и всё
took everything and destroyed the Soviet
взяли и развалили Советский
Union your Yeltsin and your
Союз ваши Ельцин и ваш
Gorbachev if it weren't for them we would still be
Горбачёв если бы не они мы до сих пор
living in a great great
жили бы в великойвеликой
country you
стране
know and so what yes what country about
понимаешь а так что да какую страну про
oh you have it so glamorous everything the
о у тебя так гламурненько так всё
phytolamp works
фитолампочка работает
yes no Andrei Vasilyevich don't pay
да не Андрей Васильевич не обращайте
attention I just didn't want to
внимания я просто не хотел вас
interrupt you excuse me
перебивать вы извините
for the first time you are all
на первый раз вы всё
right listen and in yours too there is no
правильно слушайте а у вас же тоже там
doubt your grandfather fought yes yes yes my grandfather fought
по-любому дед воевал да да да воевал дед
and my great-grandfather fought I  I also
у меня и прадед воевал я тоже так
address him like that why do you
обращаюсь ему почему вы на этом
focus your attention on this what do you
акцентрируете своё внимание на чём
focus your attention on this
на этом на акцентрируете своё внимание
I liked this I also say this
мне понравилось это я тоже говорю это
why and why do you focus and
почему а почему вы акцентируете и
say and I say
говорите и я говорю
Andrey Andrey
андрей Андрей
Vasilyevich and this And your grandfather also
Васильевич и это А у вас же тоже дед
fought in any case and your great-grandfather fought yes yes and and
воевал по-любому и прадед воевал да да
this and look I look
а и это и вот смотрите я смотрю
constantly here in the blog yes and there are
постоянно вот в бло блоге да и есть
such guys who are from Ukraine and they
такие ребята которые с Украины и они
constantly post either Vlasov or
постоянно выкладывают то Власова то ещё
someone else how do you feel about this you are a
кому вы как к этому относитесь вы же
historian so where did yours disappear
историк так куда ваша пропала
well I kind of try to communicate with you specifically
ну я как бы стараюсь конкретно с вами
well stop stop stop you just
общаться ну стоп стоп стоп вы только что
said such an articulate
ээ сказали целое такое членораздельное
sentence so rather complicated and not
предложение такое довольно сложное и ни
once did you say
одного раза не сказали
Andrey Vasilyevich
андрей Васильевич
cool excuse me please excuse me
прикольно извините пожа извините
please if something confuses you
пожалуйста если там что-то вас смущает
Andrey Vasilyevich
андрей Васильевич
can I repeat the question yes I allow you to
можно повторить вопрос да разрешаю вам
repeat the question thank you very much you are so
повторить вопрос спасибо большое вы так
kind and this is in fact look
любезны и это на самом деле смотрите у
your grandfathers also fought yes there fathers
вас же тоже деды воевали да там отцы
and beans fought also grandfathers and beans and  beans I did
и бобы воевали тоже деды и бобы и бобы я
n't mean to be rude to you please forgive me I didn't
не хотел нагрубить вам простите
mean to be rude at all well
пожалуйста не хотел ничего нагрубить ну
my grandfather was a Hero of the Soviet Union and you
у меня дед герой Советского Союза и вы
say that grandfathers fought he was a Hero of the Soviet Union
так говорите деды воевали он герой
by the way a pilot
Советского Союза между прочим лётчик
yeah Andrey Vasilyevich what do you think
ага андрей Васильевич как вы относитесь
about those that well like Vlasov
к тем что вот ну вот как вот власовым
all of these in a row yes the thing is that
вот этим вот всем подряд да дело в том
while my grandfathers were fighting in Ukraine
что пока мои деды в Украине воевали
against Hitler Russian grandfathers were in
против Гитлера российские деды были в
Vlasov's army this Andrey Vlasov
армии Власова вот этот Андрей Власов
was a Russian yes a general and his army was
россиянин был да генерал и его армия
Russian it was called the Russian
русская она так и называлась русская
Liberation Army
освободительная армия
yes unfortunately unfortunately when our
да к сожалению к сожалению когда наши
grandfathers stood and shot at the
деды да стояли и стреляли из винтовки по
Germans with a rifle the Vlasovites shot our grandfathers in the back these
немцам власовцы нашим дедам в спины
Russians there a million
стреляли вот эти русские там миллион
million Russians a million Russians a million
миллион россиян миллион россиян миллион
Russians shot our grandfathers in the back
россиян стреляло в спину нашим дедам
while they were shooting at the Germans the
пока они стреляли в немцев
Russian Liberation Army and the Russian
русская освободительная армия и Русская
Orthodox Church supported the
православная церковь поддерживала
Russian Liberation Army against the
Русскую освободительную армию против
Soviet Union for Hitler
Советского Союза за Гитлера
Andrey that's how it was and moreover what
андрей вот так вот и больше того какой
flag did it have
флаг был у
Vlasovites tricolor which is now above the
власовцев триколор который сейчас над
Kremlin why your Yeltsin your Yeltsin
Кремлём почему ваш Ельцин ельцин ваш
who sold out to America and the Nazis took the
который продался Америке и нацистам взял
red flag with the
снял с Кремля красный флаг со
star from the Kremlin the Victory banner was taken from the Kremlin and
звездой знамя Победы снял с Кремля и
hung in the Lasov tricolor Yeltsin yours is it so
повесил в ласовский триколор ельцин ваш
or not
так или не так
no again your grandfather under what flag did
нет ещё раз твой дед под каким флагом
he fight
воевал
under the Russian under what flag under the red
под русским под каким флагом под красным
or under the tricolor
или под триколором
oh don't
ай не
hang out that's how grandfathers grandfathers yes they took the
зависа вот так вот деды деды да сняли
victory banner from the Kremlin and hung the
знамя победы с Кремля и повесили
Vlasov rag hello
Власовскую тряпку здравствуйте
hello where are you from
здравствуйте вы откуда
we are from Russia and how do you communicate
мы из России а чем общаетесь
yes about everything for
да обо всём
example naki for
например наки
example
например
well I'm asking naki topic let's talk understood
ну я спрашиваю наките тему поговорим
I'm throwing out such a topic what do you
понял я вот накидываю такую тему как вы
think why Ukraine attacked Russia do you mean the
считаете зачем Украина напала на Россию
region
это вы имеете в виду регион
no Ukraine attacked Russia
нет украина напала на Россию
why why Ukraine attacked
зачем зачем Украина напала на
Russia well I don't know I'm hearing this for the first time
Россию ну не знаю я впервые такое слышу
no well now there is a war between Russia and
не ну сейчас же идёт война России и
Ukraine Russia didn't attack so
Украины россия не нападала значит напала
Ukraine attacked that's clear and why Ukraine
Украина это понятно а зачем Украина
attacked
напала
I say again  first time I heard about this I do
ещё раз говорю я впервые об этом слышал
n't understand how wait no Ukraine attacked
не понимаю как подожди не Украина напала
Russia yes it wanted to
на Россию да она что-то захотела
seize something in Russia there or there to force
захватить в России там или там заставить
something to disarm why Ukraine
что-то разоружиться почему Украина
attacked and is fighting against Russia and that's where the
напала и воюет против России а вон куда
topic is going I understand
тема идёт понял
you well the same thing the third time I can
вас ну тот же самое третий раз могу
answer the same thing well and who do you
ответить то же самое хорошо а как вы
think is to blame for the fact that Ukraine
считаете кто виноват в том что Украина
attacked Russia only Ukraine or both
напала на Россию только Украина или обе
sides the
стороны
fourth time the same thing
четвёртый раз то же
this is compromising you I don't know
самое это компрометирующее вы я не знаю
what you're pulling out of me you're probably just
что из меня тянете вы наверное просто
writing down what I'm writing down yes I want to
записываете что Я записываю да я хочу
understand look Ukraine attacked
понять смотрите вот Украина напала на
Russia is only Ukraine to blame for this
Россию в этом виновата только Украина
or Well in a conflict there are always two sides to blame
или Ну в конфликте же всегда две стороны
yes that means Russia is also to blame that
виноваты да значит Россия тоже виновата
Ukraine attacked it so Ukraine didn't attack anyone
так что Украина ни на кого не нападала
Ukraine attacked Russia that's a fact
украина напала на Россию это факт
I don't know with such a fact I'm not familiar
не знаю с таким фактом я не знаком
so who attacked whom
так а кто на кого напал
then well no one attacked anyone it
тогда ну никто ни на кого не напал
turns out no well no one if no one
получается нет ну никто если бы никто ни
attacked anyone then no one would have
на кого не напал то бы никто ни против
fought against anyone and since Ukraine is fighting with
кого не воевал а раз Украина воюет с
Russia that means Ukraine attacked Russia
Россией значит Украина напала на Россию
Ukraine  forced to attack Russia well
украину вынудили напасть на на Россию ну
look agree yes that Russia wanted
смотри согласись да что Россия хотела
peace and Ukraine wanted war therefore
мира а Украина хотела войны поэтому
Ukraine attacked Russia it is obvious
Украина напала на Россию это очевидно
everyone understands it but I do not understand only one thing
это все понимают да непонятно мне только
: what goals does Ukraine pursue with its
одно: какие цели преследует Украина
attack on Russia
своим нападением на Россию
again what goals does Ukraine pursue with
ещё раз какие цели Украина преследует
its attack on Russia what does it want to achieve
своим нападением на Россию что она хочет
what does it want to achieve
что хочет
at all for the first time I hear that
добиться вообще впервые слышу что
Ukraine is attacking somewhere in the sense well
Украина нападает куда-то в смысле ну
Ukrainian look Ukrainian missile
украинские смотрите украинская ракета
fired at the territory of Russia Ukrainian
обстреляла территорию России украинские
sabotage Dergiya entered the territory of
диверсионные Дергия зашли на территорию
Russia in the border villages yes there they
России в приграничные сёла да там
shouted in Ukraine Nagilyaku Putin yes that
кричали в Украине Нагиляку Путин да то
is Ukraine was not preparing and attacked
есть Украина на готовилась и напала на
Russia the question why what are the goals well this is now already
Россию вопрос зачем цели какие
close well it did
ну вот это вот уже теперь близко было ну
not attack as it did not attack attacked and
не нападало как не нападало напало и
now look they are shelling the territory of the
сейчас смотрите обстреливают территорию
Russian Federation with drones the Kursk
Российской Федерации дронами курскую
region was captured
область захватила
why did the Ukrainian invaders attack
почему украинские захватчики да напали
Russia no longer captured everything no
на Россию уже не захватило уже всё нет
now it has moved to the Belgorod region
теперь в Белгородскую область
it turns out why Why did
переместилась получается почему Почему
Ukraine attack Russia the most important
Украина напала на Россию самый главный
question well we lived peacefully two fraternal
вопрос ну мы жили мирно два братских
Slavic peoples we are generally in the Soviet
славянских народа мы вообще в Советском
Union  all 15 Slavic republics lived
Союзе все 15 славянских республик жили
Estonians Ukrainians Kazakhs Russians yes
эстонцы украинцы казахи русские да все
we are all brothers Slavs like all together
мы братья славяне типа все вместе против
fought against Hitler yes all Orthodox
Гитлера воевали да все православные
why did we Ukraine attack Russia after all this did
почему мы Украина напали на Россию после
not attack Ukraine how did not
не нападала Украину россия как не
attack Well look when Yeltsin and
нападала ну смотрите когда Ельцин с
Gorbachev destroyed the USSR Ukraine began to
Горбачёвым развалили СССР Украина стала
live separately together with the Americans
жить отдельно вместе с американцами
was friends with Europe Yes
дружила Европой да
they took it so that Ukraine would
они взяли сделали так чтобы Украина
attack Russia Since 1914 they
напала на Россию с четырнадцатого года
made Maidan specially the American
специально Майдан сделали американское
government expelled Yanukovych overthrew
правительство изгнали Януковича свергли
began to shell Donetsk-Lugansk Crimea
начали обстреливать Донецк- Луганск Крым
and then attacked Russia why
и потом напали на Россию зачем
man you are probably smoking something I have
мужчина вы наверное что-то курите я уже
one answer for you and so what do you smoke Well
вам отвечать одно и так что кури ну
really there is a war going on Look since
реально идёт война смотри с
1914 Ukrainian aggression
четырнадцатого года украинская агрессия
against Russia Well this is the OSCE Minsk
против России ну это ж ОБСЕ Минские
agreements we understand everything we know everything
соглашения всё всё понимаем мы всё знаем
You from 1914 to
вы с четырнадцатого по двадцать второй
1922 yours there on the outskirts Well and Russia were
год своих там на окраине ну и Россию
shelling Russia and now
обстреливали Россию и решили теперь
look in 1922 they decided even
смотри в двадцать втором году решили ещё
more Russia  attack yes why the question
больше Россию напасть да зачем вопрос
what is the goal of Ukraine that it attacks
какая цель у Украины что она нападает на
Russia
Россию
I don't know what the goal is nowhere it didn't
я не знаю какая цель никуда она не
attack well how didn't attack
нападала ну как не нападала
I don't know nowhere it didn't attack and there were
я не знаю никуда не нападала и были ж
plans yes there were also Lukashenko
планы да было на вот ещё Лукашенко
showed from which sides the
показывал с каких сторон готовилось
attack was being prepared yes from four sides there was a
нападение да с четырёх сторон был
laptop in which a laptop was found in
ноутбук в котором найден ноутбук в
which all the plans for the attack were all this is all
котором все планы нападения были это ж
clear Ukraine attacked it is already
всё всё ясно украина напала это уже
simply impossible to deny it everyone
отрицать уже просто невозможно уже все
knows this everyone saw yes everyone understands already
это знают все видели да все понимают уже
Trump even you say yes that Ukraine
Трамп даже говоришь да что Украина
attacked everyone understands the question remains the
напала все понимают вопрос остаётся
most important thing why Ukraine attacked a
самое главное зачем Украина напала на
nuclear state
ядерное государство
I will tell you briefly and clearly
я тебе коротко и ясно
8 years to watch death how long have you been Ukraine
скажу 8 лет смотреть смерти как вы долго
bombed Donbass for 88 years and
вот Украина 88 лет бомбила Донбасс а
then began to bomb Russia why
потом начала бомбить Россию зачем
Ukraine attacked Russia it attacked
Украина напала на Россию она напала на
Donbass first Ukraine attacked Crimea and now
Донбасс сначала Украина на Крым а теперь
then it went and attacked Russia again why
потом взяла и напала ещё на Россию зачем
yes it didn't attack yes it didn't attack well
да не нападал да она как не нападала ну
look first Ukraine
смотри сначала Украина обстреливала
only shelled Donbass now Belgorod is also
только Донбасс теперь Белгород ещё
shelling
обстреливает
Kursk Krasnodar
курск Краснодар
Ryazan well it attacked look first there
Рязань ну напала она смотри сначала
was only an alley of angels  in Donbass and
аллея ангелов была только на Донбассе а
now in Kursk region what a bunch of
теперь в Курской области какая олеища
angels just angels avenue there stupidly
ангелов просто проспект ангелов там тупо
there stupidly the city of Suzha was destroyed Belgorod is
там тупо город Сужа уничтожен белгород
suffering in general Stagonrogin base
вообще страдает стагонрогин базу
was destroyed this oil depot Ryazan in general
разнесли эту нефтебазу рязань вообще
in short all why
короче всё зачем
small dirty tricks or what why explain to me
пакости мелкие что ли зачем объясни мне
just why Ukraine attacks a nuclear
просто зачем Украина нападает на ядерную
power so you explain to me why pa
державу так это ты мне объясни зачем па
I don't know I don't know look I'm a citizen of
я не знаю я не знаю смотри я гражданин
Ukraine I want you to at least
Украины я хочу чтобы вы мне хотя бы
maybe explain to me you have all
может объяснили у вас у нас закрыты все
these normal TV channels closed you understand there is
эти телеканалы нормальные понимаете нет
nothing oppositional and
ничего оппозиционного а
you just know Asia democracy
вы просто знаете азия демократии
tell me do you have the right information
расскажите у вас правильная информация
telegrams instagrams tell me why what do they
телеграмы инстаграмы скажите зачем что у
write on you why Ukraine attacked Russia did
вас пишут зачем Украина напала на Россию
n't attack well how didn't
не нападала
attack what did you mean didn't attack they tell you attacked in
нападала тебе говорят напала в
2014 Ukraine
четырнадцатом году Украина на свои
attacked its own territories everyone knows this yes and in
территории напала это все знают да а в
2022 it attacked Russia
двадцать втором напала ещё на Россию
yes it didn't attack it didn't attack it for 8 years
да не нападала не нападала она 8 лет
Ukraine attacked Ukraine and bombed itself it
Украина напала на Украину и бомбила сама
bombed itself for 8 years Ukraine and in 2019
себя сама себя бомбила 8 лет Украина а
she got bored she
на девятый год ей стало скучно она
attacked Ukraine
напала на Украину
you sent
вас послал
the Westerners and you for 8
западенцев и вы его 8
years well came to stand up for him and now you for us
лет ну пришли заступиться и теперь вас
we attacked look we
вы за мы мы напали смотри мы 8 лет
attacked ourselves for 8 years Ukraine on Here everything is
нападали сами на себя украина на Тут всё
clear here everything is logical that Ukraine
понятно тут всё логично то что Украина
attacked itself it's all
нападала сама на себя это всё
according to The dude
по У чувака
got carried away I found a new topic so come on you
мозкипел я нашёл новую тему так давай ты
like subscribe comment hello
лайк подпска комент привет ты
where are you from I'm from the Saratov region cool
откуда я с Саратовской области прикольно
Engels
энгельс
you're from Angels my father is from Angels
ты с Ангельса у меня родом из Ангельса
and Engels is not far away I got it well I
отец а не до Энгельса далеко понял ну я
go there often he he was a pilot and he was
там бываю часто он он лётчиком был и его
sent to
отправили в
Dnepropetrovsk under the Union he served here and then the
Днепропетровск он тут служил и потом
Union fell apart he is here I
Союз развалился он тут
heard something somewhere that Dnepropetrovsk and
проскакивала что Днепропетровск и
Saratov are the city of Gemini I don't know if it's true
Саратов город Близнецы не знаю правда
or not but they were there but there
или нет да они же таки были да там южмаш
was Yuzhmash Rakeneta and it turns out they
стоял ракетнета и получается он они
made these planes too bombers
делали эти самолёты тоже бомбардировщики
and he flew to Engels then their  they transferred it
и он в Энгельс летал потом их перекинули
to Dnepropetrovsk and then urgently yes, so that all
в Днепропетровск а потом сро да чтоб всё
this would be
это из
transferred from Russia to Ukraine and then and
России в Украину передавали а потом а
then the Union fell apart and in short and that's it and he
потом Союз распался и короче и всё и он
stayed here and that's it It's sad of course that the
остался тут и всё по Печально конечно
Union fell apart damn well you know it's
что Союз распался блин ну это это знаешь
this Lenin of yours to blame oh not
это виноват вот этот Ленин ваш ой не
Lenin but Yelnya and Gorbachev
Ленин а Ельн и и Горбачёв
it all started because look how it
всё началось потому что смотри вот как
started yes communists China
начиналось да коммунисты Китай
communists yes what did they achieve yes in
коммунисты да чего они достигли да
general
вообще
it was when in eighty-five we had
это когда в восемьдесят пятом у нас было
everything there yes
всё там да
all this that the
всё это что
missile had weapons well all the production was I
ракеты оружие ну всё производство было
understood yes except for butter and sour cream I understood there were no
понял да кроме масла и сметаны я понял
weapons there was no food so well I mean there
оружия было еды не было так ну в смысле
was no butter and sour cream what are you talking about what I
масла и смета не было что ты несёшь что
remember I stood in line two packs per
я помню я в очереди стоял по две пачки в
hand they gave you well they gave you everyone they
руки выдавали ну это тебе выдавали всем
gave you had to stand in line for
выдавали надо было отстоять за зубной
toothpaste stand in line even well
пастой отстоять очередь даже
so that you would buy shoes for growth they would
ну чтоб вы обувь брали на вырост обувь
buy shoes that could be bought so that
покупали что можно было купить чтобы
in 2 years you could wear them I mean the Chinese were
через 2 года носить я про то что китайцы
lagging far behind the Soviet Union yes yes well
отставали намного от Советского Союза да
it was the Americans on purpose  they
да ну это американцы же специально
destroyed the Soviet Union it was a
развалили Советский Союз это была
strategy plan of Dali's there Dezhinsky well
стратегия план Далиса там Дежинский
maybe yes all of them well it seems to me
ну может быть да всё они ну мне кажется
that this is Yeltsin and Gorbachev when
что вот это Ельцин и Горбачёв когда
they flew to America they were there in short they were taken around
летали в Америку их там короче поводили
McDonald's they were shown supermarkets
по Макдональдсам показали супермаркеты
jeans chewing gum somewhere there they bribed and that's all
джинсы жвачки где-то там подкупили и всё
they came and started Gorbachev with his
они приехали и начали горбачёв со своей
perestroika
перестройкой
for chewing gum yeah well
за жвачки разваливать да
anyway and you know what's the most
ну по-любому и знаешь что самое
interesting look
интересное вот смотри
when the Soviet Union was being destroyed
когда Советский Союз разваливали
Gorbachev and Elson no one came out to
Горбачёв с Ельсоным никто не вышел
save the Soviet Union at the rally no one of you
спасти Советский Союз на митинг никто вы
came out no one came out
не выходили никто не выходил
and you came out I was generally little I was
а вы выходили я вообще маленький был мне
10 years old when out the windows well I
10 лет было когда в окна ну я такой же
was the same and how old are you 16 not seriously
был а вам сколько лет 16 не серьёзно
how old are you seriously what year were you
сколько вам лет серьёзно какого года
born
рождения
ninety-nine okay let's have a
девяносто девятого да ладно давай
normal conversation what year were you
нормально пообщаемся с какого ты года
born or or or
рождения или или или
I was born in eighty-first what year were you born well
я восемьдесят первого года рождения ты
I'm the same my husband is a little
ну я такого же муж чуть
older year
постарше год
and birth that is good then look the
и рождения то есть хорошо то смотри
question is
вопрос такой
we lived  15 Slavic republics all
мы жили 15 славянских республик все
one Rus' yes
единая Русь такая да против Гитлера
our grandfathers fought against Hitler yes we are all brothers
воевали наши деды да мы все братья
Slavs Ukrainians Belarusians Kazakhs there
славяне украинцы белорусы казахи там
Tatars Chechens Estonians yes and then hop and
татары чеченцы эстонцы да а потом гоп и
Gorbachev divided us into 15
разделил нас Горбачёв на 15
republics why did he do it
республик зачем он это сделал
and what does Gorbachev have to do with it well under Gorbachev the
а при чём тут Горбачёв ну при Горбачёве
Soviet Union collapsed
же развалился Советский Союз
each republic seceded well
каждая республика отделилась ну потому
because Gorbachev gave look if the
что Горбачёв дал смотри если бы
ruler had said no
правитель сказал нет
brought in special forces and Gorbachev said: "Yes" and
ввёл спецназ и А Горбачёв сказал: "Да" а
each each seceded well Gorbachev
каждый каждый отделился ну Горбач
Gorbachev indulged this well
Горбачёв потакал этому
why did Ukraine secede - that's for me A
ну зачем Украина отделилась-то мне вот А
because Russia seceded
потому что Россия отделилась
from what Russia well you have the first - it was
от чего россия ну у вас же первый - это
Yeltsin who proclaimed on July 12
Ельцин провозгласил 12 июля
ninetieth year the very first everyone was
девяностого года самый первый все
afraid of the republic and he went and
боялись республики а он взял и
proclaimed the RSFSR declaration of
провозгласил РСФСР декларацию о
state sovereignty of the RSFSR and that's it
государственном суверенитете РСФСР и всё
and then everyone started well sovereignty yes and that's it
и тогда все начали ну суверенитет да и
and everyone started with  sovereignty to play
всё и все начали с суверенитета играться
and everything like that everything well and how did we separate
и всё вот так всё ну а как мы отделились
and we with this and then and we are accomplices and in
и мы этим и потом и мы причастниками и в
Belovezhskaya Pushcha then who signed and
в Беловежской пуще потом кто подписал и
Eltsin signed that everything the Soviet Union does not exist
Эльцин подписал что всё Советского Союза
he that the Soviet Union does not exist but we did not
он что Советского Союза нет но мы же не
separate se well how did he he betrayed the
отделяли се ну как он он предал
Soviet Union he said that everything like well
Советский Союз он сказал что всё типа ну
look if Russia separated from the
смотри если бы Россия отделилась от
Soviet
Советского
Union now that's not so look Russia no look look
Союза сейчас вон не так смотри Рос нет
Russia Ukraine
смотри смотри россия Украина
and Belarus left the Soviet Union
и Беларусь вышли из Советского Союза
when they signed in
когда подписали в Беловежском ээ в
Belovezhskaya Pushcha an agreement that they are
Беловежской пуще соглашение что они
independent countries yes the very
независимые страны да сам самый
last of the Soviet Union left
последний Советского Союза вышел
Kazakhstan everything it is the very last everyone
Казахстан всё он самый послед все
ran away to Kazakhstan I am the only one
разбежались в Казахстан я тут один
left here and also left well that's it and here is an
остался и тоже вышел ну это такое а тут
interesting question how does it happen that
вот интересный вопрос как получается что
Yes wait you wait wait how
Да подожди ты подожди подожди как Россия
can Russia leave the Soviet Union if
может из выйти из Советского Союза если
it is the predecessor of the Soviet Union no it is
она предшественник Советского Союза нет
part of the Soviet No it is part of the
она она часть Советского Нет она часть
Soviet look the Soviet Union was part of
Советско смотри Советский Союз входила
15 republics look why Russia
15 республик вот смотри почему Россия
paid all the debts for the Soviet Union
платила все долги за Советский Союз
because the state
потому что государство
A
А
yes look in the Soviet Union there were 15
да смотри в Советском Союзе было 15
republics of Russia Russia was one of them
республик России россия была одна из них
so here is another question why all the
так вот другой вопрос почему всё
legacy of the Soviet Union Russia about
наследие Советского Союза Россия про
now they can't even make airplanes in the
сейчас даже самолёты не могут делать в
Soviet Union to buy imported airplanes
Советском Союзе чтобы импортные самолёты
shame
покупали позор
let's google about airplanes how many how
давай загуглим про самолёты сколько
many were produced per year to
Сколько выпустили за год
Ukraine and not given away yes what does Ukraine have in
Украине а на отдали да причём Украина в
Russia look in
России смотри в России советских вот про
Russia Soviet now tell me about Ukraine they stole
Россию ты мне расскажи про Украину у
everything here they stole
разворовали тут всё разворовали
and why in Russia they stole why was there
а почему в России разворовали почему был
nothing in Ukraine look in Ukraine there is nothing
в Украине ничего нет украине смотри в
what is left in Russia
Украине ничего нет что осталось в России
aircraft manufacturing
самолётостроения
Ukraine became the richest yes everything was
украина вышла самый богатой да всё у нас
stolen from us everything was taken abroad America
всё разворовали вывезли за рубеж америка
America did it on purpose explain
америка сделала это специально объясни
who stole Russia yes nothing was
кто разворовал Россию да ничего не
stolen and how many how many airplanes will
разворовал а сколько сколько самолётов
you make per year well how many are
вы сделаете в год
needed we will make how
ну сколько надо столько и сделаем ну
many at least four are there
сколько хотя бы четыре есть
yes I can't say anything
да ничего не могу сказать ты мне
tell me about Ukraine so Ukraine everything
расскажи про Украину так Украина всё
Ukraine is a poor country nothing was
украина нищая страна тут ничего
stolen here everything was cut up into machine tools
разворовали всё порезали на станки
taken to America the Americans made it
вывезли в Америку американцы сделали в
first  3 years these from ninety-one to
первые 3 года эти с девяносто первого по
ninety-four and you are afraid to
девяносто четвёртый а ты боишься
answer why Russia yes it is the
ответить почему же Россия да она
successor if the USSR yes you say yes
наследник если СССР да ты говоришь да
where did it go all these
куда онала все эти технологии
aircraft manufacturing technologies and so on
самолётостроения и так дальше
yes build an airplane builds how
да строить самолёт строит сколько
much look at Alice ask zero I
сколько посмотри у Алисы спроси ноль не
can not now I have one telepostal
могу сейчас у меня один телепостальные
everyone is
все
sleeping deceptions zero so zero because Yes
спят обманы ноль так ноль потому что Да
super superjet whose airplane what superjet
супер суперджет чей самолёт какой
your superjet flies how much of
суперджет суперджет ваш летает сколько
it was built come on show how much of that
его построили давай покажи сколько того
superjet was built how much here you yourself are on a
суперджета построили сколько вот ты сам
bender how much so you say all
загули сколько так ты же говоришь всё
zero
ноль
now come on now I am making a voice
сейчас давай сейчас я делаю голосового
assistant and now let's ask
помощника и сейчас спросим
in what year ask
в каком году спросить
yes in general here for the entire history of Russia
да вообще вот за за всю историю России
not here come on let's take last year well
не вот давай вот прошлый год возьмём
you I am telling you you are broadcasting for
ну ты я тебе говорю ты вот вещаешь для
your people damn for the Ukrainian people
своего народа блин для украинского ты
where did you run away to tell me yourself wait
сам куда сбежал-то мне расскажи подожди
wait Romanians so well from Romania to
подожди румы так ну вот из Румынии
deceive people such to yourself
обманывать народ такое себе
you understand that you will be pecked to death in
ты же понимаешь что тебя там заклюют в
this in your own country
этом в своей стране
now now so
сейчас сейчас
who  for which let's ask for the twenty-
так кто за какой давай за двадцать
fourth now it's already the
четвёртый того спросим сейчас уже
twenty-fifth
двадцать пятый
yes okay I
да о'кей
answer
отвечаю
okay Google please tell me how many
о'кей Google скажи пожалуйста сколько
Superjet planes were built in Russia in
самолётов Суперджет построено в России в
24th year
24м году
I answer in 2024 not a
отвечаю в 2024 году в России не
single
построили ни один
Superjet was built in Russia because
суперджет потому что
Russia destroyed the USSR
Ру развалили СССР
so I'll tell you
значит тебе скажу
hello hello and how do you
здравствуйте здравствуйте а чем
communicate yes it doesn't
общаетесь
matter it's cool where are
да без разницы прикольно сами
you from Russia it's cool where are you from Ukraine
вы откуда из Украины
too
тоже неплохо
not bad it's not bad it's good well in
это не неплохо это хорошо
different ways everyone so it is what
ну по-разному каждый попри так оно есть
brought you to chat roulette
что вас привело в чат рулетка
yes I just became listenable so I came in
да просто слушен стал вот зашёл
how do you feel about the fact that Russia will leave
как относишься к тому что Россия выдет с
Ukraine they are fraternal peoples
Украины братские же народы
well there is a certain plus there are
ну есть определённый плюс есть
certain minuses what are the
определённые минусы
pluses what are the
какие плюсы какие минусы
minuses well the minuses are that unfortunately
ну минусы в то что к сожалению гибнут
people are dying here no one here
люди этого у нас никто здесь не
supports this not a single person pluses well
поддерживает ни одного человека плюсы ну
and pluses unfortunately
а плюсы
Ukraine is a Nazi
к сожалению Украина - это нацистское
state so now at the
государство поэтому сейчас-то на данный
moment I mean so well
момент я имею в виду поэтому
somehow no well you agree that
ну как-то так не ну вы же согласны что
Ukraine is not a state at all  it is
Украина вообще не государство она
controlled by the Anglo-Saxons directly well
управляется англосаксами напрямую
here yes here I agree yes but therefore it would be
ну здесь да здесь согласен да по поэтому
logical not to attack
тут логично было бы не нападать
look at the brotherly Slavic people
посмотрите ээ братский славянский народ
Ukrainians in the ninety-first year when the
украинцы в девяносто первом году когда
Soviet Union collapsed the Anglo-Saxons
Советский Союз развалился англосакцы
took control and management under their control and
взяли под свой контроль и управление и
therefore uh Russia now by killing the
поэтому ээ Россия сейчас убивая
Ukrainian brothers Slavs it does not make the Anglo-Saxons
украинцев братьев славян она не делает
worse yes it kills its
англосаксом хуже да она убивает своих
Russian Slavs and Ukrainian Slavs and the
русских славян и украинских славян а
Anglo-Saxons rub their hands it would be more illogical and
англосакцы потирают руку нелогичнее было
Oreshnikov well
и орешников ну
listening what can be said now
слушении что можно сказать вот сейчас к
unfortunately Ukraine acts as how to
сожалению Украина выступает как вот как
say in the nineties probably lived
сказать в девяностые наверное жили
you know what the nineties are
знаете что такое девяностые года
right yes yes and when there was a
правильно дада вот и когда вот там двор
courtyard going out to another courtyard there they were fighting there somewhere there
на двор выходил там месились там где-то
nasmer somewhere not nasmer there so they acted yes
там насмер где-то не насмер там так вот
now unfortunately
выступали да вот сейчас к сожалению вот
Ukraine acts as such a
Украина это выступает в роли вот такой
local showdown when Ukraine is
вот местной разборки когда Украина - это
just some courtyard somewhere yes so
просто какой-то двор где-то да так
look Ukraine is not Suba it's bad
смотри Украина - это не Субе это бейд
everything yes here it is clear since the ninety-first
всё да тут понятно с девяносто первого
year when yours  Yeltsin and Gorbachev
года когда вот ваши Ельцин и Горбачёв
destroyed the Soviet Union, giving Ukraine
развалили Советский Союз отдав Украину
to be torn apart by the Anglo-Saxons, it was
на растерзание англосаксом это было
very shameful, yes, all 15 of our
очень позорно да вы все 15 наших
Slavic republics, Ukrainians, Kazakhs,
славянских республик украинцы казахи
Lithuanians, Russians, we were all Slavs,
литовцы русские все мы были славяне
brothers, we fought against Hitler, and then,
братья против Гитлера воевали да и тут
in short, your Gorbachev and
короче Горбачёв ваш и
Yeltsin said: "The Soviet
Ельцин да взяли и сказали: "Советский
Union will no longer be, uh, Americans,
Союз это больше не будет ээ американцы
take all these republics." The Americans
забирайте все эти республики" американцы
took them, that is, in 1991, you
забрали то есть вы в девяносто первом
gave us to the Americans, Gorbachev
году отдали нас американцам горбачёв
withdrew troops from
вывел войска из
East Berlin, from Germany, yes, NATO
восточного Берлина из Германии да нато
moved to the east, in short, took and
подвинулась короче на восток взяла
sent tentacles here, and now, instead of
пустила сюда щупальца а теперь вы вместо
giving battle
того чтобы дать бой
to the Anglo-Saxons, you are killing your own
англосаксам вы убиваете своих же братьев
Slavic brothers, well, why is that so, the
славян ну почему так
question is that why, in the
вот вопрос всё в том что почему вот в
same external management, your
том же самом внешнем управлении ваши
presidents went and did
президенты пошли
not threaten Russia, that's right,
не угрожать то же самое России правильно
stop, stop, stop again, it is not Zelensky who is
так стоп стоп ещё раз это не Зеленский
threatening, it is the Anglo-Saxons who are threatening,
угрожает это угрожает англосаксие
Zelensky is simply an official who was
зеленский он просто чиновник которого
appointed  Anglo-Saxons and he will simply voice it, he does
поставили англосакси и он просто озвучит
not accept anything, we do not
он ничего не принимает мы ничего не
decide anything in Ukraine, it is all the Anglo-Saxons
решаем в Украине это всё англосаксы
who, because of your
которые из-за вашего
Yeltsin and Gorbachev, yes, captured
Ельцина и как его Горбачёва да захватили
Ukraine, look, you destroyed the
Украину смотрите вы да развалили
Soviet Union, did not defend it, gave it to the
Советский Союз не отстояли его дали ээ
Americans and Europeans to advance NATO
американцам и европейцам продвинуть НАТО
to the east, then left the
на восток тогда вышли из
Warsaw Pact countries, withdrew troops,
стран Варшавского блока вывели войска
destroyed the Berlin Wall, instead of
разрушили берлинскую стену вместо того
moving tanks to the English Channel, yes, you moved
чтобы двинуть танки на Ламанш да вы
American Abrams to
американские абрамсы пододвинули к
Poland or the Baltics, that's all, and now,
в Польшу или Прибалтику всё а теперь
instead of realizing your mistake,
вместо того чтобы осознать свою ошибку
realizing that the Russian people betrayed their
осознать что русский народ предал своих
brothers, the Slavs, Kazakhs, Lithuanians, Moldovans,
братьев славян казахов литовцев молдован
Ukrainians, Estonians, betrayed all of us Slavs,
украинцев эстонцев всех нас славян
and instead of taking and
предал и вместо того чтобы взять и
saying: "So America and the Anglo-Saxons,
сказать: "Так Америка и англосакцы
give us everything back, let our Slavic brothers
возвращайте нам всё пусть братья славяне
live not under your yoke," no,
живут не под вашим иго" нет вы вместо
instead of taking Alaska, New York,
того чтобы взять по Аляске по Нью-Йорку
Chicago, Los Angeles,
по Чикаго по Лос-Анджелесу по
Sacramento, you took and are demolishing Bakhmut,
Сакрамента вы взяли и сносите Бахмут
Kharkov, Mariupol, Slavic cities  with the
Харьков Мариуполь славянские города с
Russian-speaking population, the Russian-speaking
русскоязычным населением русскоязычным
Slavs who say in Russian
славяне которые на русском языке
: "You are destroying them," and
говорят: "Вы их уничтожаете" а
the Anglo-Saxons sit and say: "What kind of
англосакцы сидят и говорят: "Какие эти
Russians are these?"  So, will
россияне?" Вот
you go? Okay, we'll go
так разве вы пойдё Хорошо мы пойдём
further, let's say you'll go with us to the Anglo-Saxons.
дальше допустим на англосаксо вы с нами
No, if you had gone not to
пойдёте нет так если бы вы пошли не на
Ukraine but to the Anglo-Saxons, all of
Украину а на англосаксов сразу вся бы
Ukraine would have supported us. We've been
Украина только поддержала мы с девяносто
suffering under this oppression since 1991.
первого года мучаемся под этим гнётом
Remember when Mazlin Albright
помните приезжала Маzlinлин Олбрайт
came to Ukraine, and all those
приезжала в Украину да приезжали все эти
convicts Rice came, and they put their tentacles out here.
кандализы Райс они же тут щупальца свои
We've been waiting since 1991 for the
пустили мы с девяносто первого года
attack on Berlin, when it will be on the
ждали когда будет бросок на Берлин когда
English Channel, when the tanks will go, in
будет на Ламанш когда танки пойдут
short, to Brussels, and Russia took and
короче на ээ Брюсль а Россия взяла и нам
stabbed us in the back. We were preparing. We were preparing.
нож в спину мы готовились готовились
Why did we want to join the European Union and NATO?
почему мы хотели в Евросоюз и в НАТО вти
We wanted to destroy them from within because we
мы хотели изнутри их развалить потому
see that Russia can't do it from within and that's it,
что видим Россия не может изнутри и всё
and together with Russia we would have moved Belarus,
и вместе с Россией бы двинулись белорусь
everything is holy Rus', and we are all of you. And you
всё святая Русь мы все а вы взяли и
just stabbed us in the back instead of
просто нож в спину вместо того чтобы
attacking Berlin together, like our grandfathers in
вместе напасть на Берлин как деды в
1945. In short, you stabbed us in the back,
сорок пятом взяли короче и в спину нам
and like now.  you see
ударили и как теперь понимаете
the Anglo-Saxons are now rubbing their hands
англосаксы сейчас потирают руки
American soldiers are drinking coffee at the
американские солдаты да пьют кофе на
base in Guantanamo and in Pearl
базе в Гуантанамо и в Перл
Harbor and Russian soldiers are dying in
Харборе а российские солдаты умирают в
nameless ravines and what the American
безымянных оврагах и что американский
soldier says: "Good Ivan good very good
солдат говорит: "Гуд Иван good very good
Ivan" well
Иван" вот так
listen first of all now not only the
ну слушай во-первых сейчас у не то что
American soldiers now every soldier
американские солдат сейчас каждый солдат
they will run away in horror from
они будут в ужасе разбегаться от кого бы
anyone so what are we talking about here so why
то ни было поэтому тут о чём говорим-то
look I don't understand why why
так зачем смотри я не понимаю зачем
Putin and you are sending your
зачем Путин и вы пускаете свои войска
Slavic troops yes Vyatichi Buryatichi
славянские да Вятичий Бурятичий
Chechens all these tribes yes to kill the
Чеченичие вот эти все племена да убивать
Slavs of Mariupol Bakhmut Kharkov well
славян Мариуполя Бахмута Харькова то ж
just look you take it very simply on the
просто смотри берёте очень просто по
map yes through uh Russia through the
карте да через ээ Россию
Baltic
через Балтику
Poland
Польшу
directly and that's it
прямым и всё
listen you will
так слушайте вы же
lose you don't look if Well you
сольёте вы не смотри если Ну вы же
will run away you understand well you yourself should
убежите понимаешь ну сам должен
understand perfectly well what you uh you will
прекрасно понимать что же вы ээ вас вы
put you under the one who is stronger right
положите под того кто сильнее правильно
right if you take Berlin everything
правильно если вы возьмёте Берлин всё
Ukraine I have already prepared I already have the
Украина я уже приготовил я уже держу
number on  I keep the car number here in the
номер на машину номер держу вот в
Kursk region as if yes I keep it and
Курской области как будто да я держу и
wait as soon as Russian tanks enter
жду как только русские танки входят в
Berlin yes I immediately hang this number on the car
Берлин да я сразу вешаю на машину этот
and say: "Hurray we are Slavic brothers yes
номер и такой: "Ура мы братья славяне да
yes you are in the Kursk region I am
да ты же Курской области находишься я ж
grandfather grandfather on a stick in short I will even draw it
деда деда на палке короче даже нарисую
right away I understood you of course I
сразу я понял тебя конечно я тебя
understand you that you are here this is tsutsm
понимаю то что ты здесь это цуцм своим
doing your business I understand you perfectly
делом занимаешься я тебя прекрасно
so here the question is what the
понимаю поэтому здесь вопрос-то в чём
question is why Russia is not fighting the
вопрос в том почему Россия не воюет с
Anglo-Saxons
англосаксами
well because now we will conquer you we
ну потому что вот сейчас мы вас завоюем
will go further against the Anglo-Saxons so why not
пойдём дальше на англосаксов так а зачем
immediately attack the Anglo-Saxons well
сразу на англосаксов не напасть ну
because you are in our way you
потому что вы нам мешаете вы же нам
threatened us but how can we again when
угрожали а как мы можем опять же когда
you live with a neighbor when your neighbor
ты живёшь с соседом когда тебе сосед
leaves first he will give out twice will
предыду уходит сначала раздаст два раза
succeed and he does not receive an answer the
удаст при этом он ответ не получает
third time it starts with Wait
третий раз он же начинается на Подожди
so look Russia Russia spent so many planes so many guns on
так смотри Россия Россия потратила на
some cities of Donbass
какие-то города Донбасса столько
all for this
самолётов столько орудий всё за эти
money for this equipment and manpower it is possible  it
деньги за эти технику и живую силу можно
was easy to throw hats at Berlin,
было просто шапками закидать Берлин
restak like our grandfathers in 1945, erected a
рестак как деды в сорок пятом водрузить
sign over the Rikstag, everything will be harvested already, no
знамо над Рикстагом уже всё урожают
one is threatening us, and who
никто не как не угрожает а кто
supplies Ukraine with weapons, no
поставляет Украине оружие украины нам
one has threatened us, who supplies, who
никто не угрожал кто поставляет кто
supplies weapons to Ukraine, what do you think,
оружие Украине поставляет ты что думаешь
Ukraine produces these weapons itself, no,
Украина сама вырабатывает это оружие нет
no, of course, Ukraine has long
да нет конечно в Украину уже давно
been under someone's thumb, they are like this, look, yes, the
взлегла уже под кого-то они так смотри
Germans are sitting in
да Украине немцы да немцы сидят в
Berlin and saying:
Берлине и говорят:
"Khodemargu, yes, they say that Rus' is
"Ходемаргу так да они говорят что Русь
still a Hyundai, and it supplies its weapons,
ещё хендехо да и поставляет свои оружие
so that the Russians die at Kursk, do you
да чтобы русские погибали под Курском
understand who is telling us this?" Who are the
понимаешь кто кто нам это говорит?" Кто
Germans, well, look, the Germans are just laughing,
немецкие ну смотри немцы просто смеются
yes, German tanks
уже да э немецкие танки под Курском
are killing Russians at Kursk, they are just enjoying
убивают русских они просто кайфуют от
it, you understand what I mean, who
это ты же понимаешь о чём я вот кто тебе
told you that the Germans, yes, I have a friend in
сказал что немцы да у меня знакомый в
Germany, he says: "Oh, this is good,"
Германии он говорит: "О е я это good" у
I have a lot of friends in Germany
меня очень много знакомых Германии
who tell you, yeah, but we think that
которые говорят тебе угу а мы думаем что
everything is different, show it like this  look look
всё по-другому показывать так смотри
well why won't Russia do it so that
смори ну почему Россия не сделает так
nothing is supplied to Ukraine
чтобы ничего да не поставляли Украине
so I'll tell you I'll just explain to me why
так я тебе я мне просто объясни почему
look you're saying we had to
вот смотри ты говоришь мы куда-то должны
go somewhere explain to me
были зайти объясни мне да
why your Zelensky fingers
почему твой Зеленский пальцы
well don't hang around damn so interesting
ну не зависай блин такой интересный
hung up bombasimo like subscribe comment
завис бомбисимо лайк подписка коммент
hello hello where are you
здравствуйте здравствуйте вы откуда
from Moscow I understand what you're talking about Muscovite well about
из Москвы понял о чём общаетесь Москвич
anything what do you
ну о чём угодно
think Greenland whose well
как считаете Гренландия чья
now at the moment Denmark yeah
ну сейчас в данный момент Дании угу
got it and whose should it be well
понял а чья должна быть
if it's fair then Denmark
ну если по справедливости то Дании
of course but something tells me that
конечно но что-то мне подсказывает что
it will probably
независимость она наверное
get independence what will happen next what do you
получит что дальше будет
think why did Russia attack
как считаете почему Россия напала на
Ukraine and not the Anglo-Saxons I
Украину а не на англосаксов
mean well how far from the Anglo-Saxons well
в смысле ну как до англосаксов далеко
including in Ukraine they
ну в том числе на Украине уже они тоже
were already there so the thing is that it just
были так что дело в том что просто
somehow turns out that the Anglo-Saxons
как-то так получается что англосаксы
sit and rub their hands and the Slavs
сидят потирают ручки а славяне друг
kill each other well
друга убивают
this is the Anglo-Saxon strategy unfortunately
ну это стратегия Англосакса к сожалению
they always worked so well he
они всегда так хорошо работали он
how many Indians 100 million Indians were killed with the
сколько индусов 100 млн индусов убили с
Pakistanis  right yes of
пакистанцами правильно да так это ж
course they are still doing it yes that's
конечно они и до сих пор делают да так
why Putin I can't understand why he is
вот почему Путин не могу понять зачем он
playing along with the Anglo-Saxons and making the
подыгрывает англосаксом и делает чтобы
Slavs kill the Slavs instead of sending
славяне убивали славян вместо того чтобы
all these Vyatichi Buryatichi Chenichs
всех этих вятичей бурятичей ченичей
to Washington or London
направить на Вашингтон или Лондон
eh so why is Putin
э так почему Путин
killing again why Putin I'm
убивает ещё раз почему Путин Что-то я
already confused eh why is he playing along with the
уже запутался ээ почему поигрывает
Anglo-Saxons yes why
подытыгрывает Англосаксом да почему он
instead of attacking the Anglo-Saxons he
вместо того чтобы напасть на англосакса
attacked the Slavic brothers
напал на братьев славян
well because Turchinov
ну потому что Турчинов же начал
initially started the attack attacked the
изначально напасть напал на братьев
Slavic brothers what else could he do it was
славян что куда деваться-то было так это
n't Turchinov it was the Anglo-Saxons you know the
же не Турчинов это англосаксы вы знаете
Anglo-Saxons made the
англосаксы сделали
Maidan yes here you can even
Майдан ну да тут даже глубже можно
look deeper the Anglo-Saxons took and destroyed the USSR
смотреть англосаксы взяли развалили СССР
your this Yeltsin and eh this bald
вот ваши этот Ельцин и ээ плешивый этот
Gorbachev took and simply dissolved 15 of our Slavic
Горбачёв да взяли и 15 наших славянских
fraternal republics
братских республик просто распустили
said: "That's it, the Soviet Union is no more
сказали: "Всё нет уже больше Советского
" Gorbachev withdrew the Soviet
Союза" горбачёв вывел войска Советского
Union troops from Eastern Europe
Союза из Восточной Европы
Gorbachev gave  dismantle the Berlin Wall
горбачёв дал разобрать берлинскую стену
and withdrew troops from East Germany all
и вывел войска из Восточной Германии всё
Gorbachev no e something I don't remember Gorbachev
горбачёв не е что-то я не помню горбачёв
Gorbachev yes the walls when they broke down
горбачёв да стени когда сломали
eighty-nine still and
восемьдесят девятый год ещё ж а
eighty-nine well yes yes that's all and he
восемьдесят девятый ну да да вот и всё и
said directly: "Look NATO we are
прямо сказал: "Смотрите НАТО мы вам
giving you Eastern Europe take it back we
отдаём Восточную Европу забирайте мы
withdrew our troops" and what NATO immediately yes
свои войска вывели" и что нато сразу да
in what immediately color revolutions took place
во что сразу цветные революции прошли
there in the Czech Republic in Hungary in Poland everything is
там в Чехии в Венгрии в Польше всё и
predetermined we Ukraine yes we when there was a
предопределено мы Украина да мы же когда
vote for a referendum to
было голосование за референдум чтобы
preserve the Soviet Union all the republics
сохранить Советский Союз все республики
voted almost yes what to preserve the
проголосовали почти да что сохранить
Soviet Union and then you have the State Emergency Committee yes and
Советский Союз а потом у вас ГКЧП да и
everything in short and everything and once-once they ran away there
всё короче и всё и раз-раз разбежались
was time yes yes and it turns out that the
время было да да и получается что
Anglo-Saxons immediately took control of
англосаксы сразу же взяли под контроль
Ukraine immediately put their own here
Украину сразу же поставили сюда своих
They took Russia under control and
Они Россию взяли под контроль и Россию
took Russia under control yes yes in your
взяли под контроль да да у вас же в этом
White House the sixth floor was all
в Белом доме шестой этаж весь был в
Anglo-Saxons well I know that and
англосаксах ну это же знаю и до сих пор
there is still a sixth there I thought there were more floors  no well the
там шестой я думал больше этажей нет ну
sixth floor is where all these advisers
шестой этаж там это все эти советники
sat yes to this day your Central Bank is
сидели да до сих пор Центробанк ваш
subordinate to the Anglo-Saxons still there
подчиняется англосаксом до сих пор на
is no emphasis on Nabiullina according to your
Набиулину нету никакого упора у вас по
constitution the Central Bank essentially does not
конституции Центробанк по сути не
depend on the state and that's it and now
зависит от государства и всё и теперь
what happens instead of like
что получается вместо того чтобы как
our grandfathers in 1945 all 15
деды наши в сорок пятом все 15
Slavic republics went to Berlin yes
славянских республик пошли на Берлин да
what does Russia do kill its own people and
что делает Россия убивает своих людей и
kill Ukrainian people that is
убивает украинских людей то есть
play along with the Anglo-Saxons reduces the
подыгрывает англосаксов уменьшает
Slavic population the concept of the golden
население славянское концепция золотого
billion you know
миллиарда знаете
yes yes the Belderberg Club and so on
да да бельдербергский клуб и так дальше
they want to leave a billion on earth
они хотят оставить на земле миллиард
because there is global warming and
потому что идёт глобальное потепление и
all these coastal cities all these
все эти прибрежные города все эти
New Yorks of them yes all these Londons yes they will
Нью-Йорки их да все эти лондоны да они
all end up under
все окажутся под
water European cities will end up under
водой европейские города окажутся под
water yes there are these tornadoes and that's it and so
водой да вот там торнады эти и всё и так
on they
дальше они
consider the Ukrainian land
рассматривают украинскую землю
Belarusian and the black earth of Russia as
белорусскую и черноземье России как
fertile ground for resettlement
благодатную почву для переселения
new Khazaria you know this concert well
новая Хазария знаете вот этот концерт
I heard yes that's how it should be for them
ну я слышал да вот у них так должно быть
from the Baltic Sea Black Casper three
от Балтийское море Чёрный Касперри три
seas  this triangle is called the
море вот этот треугольник называется
Neo-Khazar triangle and this
Неохазарский треугольник да и эта
concept yes they are now specially
концепция да они сейчас специально
clearing
очищают
this territory with the hands of Russia, they are
руками России очищают эту территорию
stupidly
тупо
clearing it of people, of cities, they want a
очищают от людей от городов они хотят
concept of building new neo-tribes like this
концепцию строить новые неорода такие
they want to make a new world a new Khazaria
они хотят делать новый мир новую хазарию
they have been waiting for this for 1,000 years after
они ждали это 1.000 лет после того как
Prince
князь
Svyatoslav defeated the Khazars on the
Святослав разгромил Хазар на
Volga destroyed their city of Sarkel Belaya
Волге уничтожил ихний город Саркел Белую
Vezha and
Вежу и
Itil and that's it
Итиль и всё
and now what happens yes
и теперь что получается да что
the Anglo-Saxons are
англосаксы
getting stronger and the Slavs no the Slavs it
усиливаются а славяне нет славяне
turns out there are fewer and fewer of them becoming
получается их всё меньше и меньше стаёт
weaker and weaker all the Russian
и слабее и слабее весь весь российский
military potential that remained from the
военный потенциал который остался от
Soviet Union
Советского Союза
burned down in the war in Ukraine the fleet is at the
сгорел войне в Украине флот на
bottom the tanks are old junk left on
дне танки старьё осталось уже на
loaves he drives cars like
буханках он ездит на машинах типа на
Zhiguli
Жигулях в атаку
they all went on the attack because they were uh
они все ездили потому что они ээ на
repairable yes that's all the planes it
ремонтопригодные да вот и всё самолёты
also turns out instead of
также получается вместо того чтобы
making a forced march to the
сделать марш-бросок на
West for some reason Putin got stuck in
Запад зачем-то Путин взял и завяз в
Ukraine
Украине
moreover if Putin had made a dash
больше того если бы Путин сделал бросок
to Berlin in Ukraine the majority would
на Берлин в Украине большинство бы
supported it because now after the
поддержало это потому что сейчас после
FAB missiles fly into our cities it is
в наши города прилетают ракеты фабы
very difficult to tell people that the enemy is in
очень сложно людям сказать что враг в
Berlin because they say: "Berlin is
Берлине потому что они говорят: "Берлин
not bombing us, Berlin is helping us, but
нас не бомбит Берлин нам помогает а
Moscow is bombing us" you see what a
бомбит нас Москва" понимаете какая
transformation happened when our grandfathers
трансформация произошла когда деды наши
celebrated May 9
праздновали 9 мая
and it was normal, we all understood the
и это было нормально мы все понимали
banner over the Drechstag
знамя надрехстага мне дед
when my grandfather took me to the eternal flame from childhood, he
когда водил с детства к вечному огню
told me my grandfather took Berlin
рассказывал у меня дед брал Берлин был
too, well, he didn't raise the flag over the
тоже ну не водружал конечно флаг над
Drechstag of course because there were a lot of
Дрихстаром потому что там очень много
people there, but he participated in the battles for
людей было но участвовал в боях за
Berlin, Hero of the Soviet Union, by the way, and
Берлин герой Советского Союза кстати и
he told me: "I had tears running down my face
он мне рассказывал: "У меня слеза текла
when I was little, but now it is
тогда когда маленького была а сейчас что
not fashionable to talk about victory over
сейчас не модно говорить о победе над
Berlin because Berlin turns out to be an
Берлином потому что Берлин получается
ally of Ukraine, it helps Moscow is
союзник Украины он помогает Москва
bombing and I tried to tell people that
бомбит и я пробовал людям говорить что
yes, we are Ukrainians, Slavs, but together with
да мы украинцыславяне но мы вместе с
Moscow we burned Berlin and they tell me:
Москвой сожгли Берлин а они мне говорят:
"That was a long time ago, and now Berlin is
"Это было давно а сейчас Берлин нам
helping us, protecting us, and Moscow is bombing and I
помогает защищает а Москва бомбит и я
can't say anything" Kharkov, a friend
ничего не могу сказать" харьков знакомый
from Kharkov, I say:
из Харькова я говорю:
"Look, Moscow is our friend," and he says:
"Смотри Москва наш друг" а он говорит:
"If it's a friend, why did it drop a FAB bomb on the
"Если это друг почему она скинула на
school where my
школу в которой учился мой
child studied?"  I can't
ребёнок бомбу ФАБ?" Я не могу ему
answer him like that
ответить вот так
in school in Kharkov I don't remember something
в школу в Харькове что-то не помню
I have three questions can I ask
у меня три вопроса можно да задам
frankly yes do you believe in God yes Jesus
откровенно да вы в Бога верите да исуса
understood the second question Americans were on the
понял второй вопрос американцы были на
Moon what do you think I think no it's a
Луне как думаете думаю нет это
setup you saw how the flag like
постановка вы же видели как флаг типа
fluttered where is the atmosphere there and the
развивался откуда атмосфера там и
last question the earth is flat no
последний вопрос земля плоская нет
[laughter] the
[смех]
guy wanted to give us this about solitaire and
тип хотел навалить это нам про солитик а
we
мы ему
just
просто
bombed him subscribe to my Telegram
набомбили подпишись на мий Telegram
right now os vn and
прямо зараз ось вн а
popik this is very and very important youtube
попик це дуже и дуже важливо youtube
bans us through cards and
заганяе нас через карки в тіньовий бан и
a lot of videos are not shown to people
дуже багато відео не показуется людям
sometimes information about streams is not shown
вчасно не показуется інформація про
so that we have a
стрими тому для того щоб ми мали
quick connection subscribe right
оперативный зв'язок підпишиться прямо
now and popik there is okmdeo in telegram
зараз а попик там в телеграмі окмдео ще
also interesting and useful information  and we are
теж цікава и корисна інформація и мы
obliged to maintain constant
повинні з вами тримати постійний
operational communication with you, regardless of
оперативный зв'язок незалежно від того
whether we show you about this YouTube, glory to
чи покаже вам про це YouTube слава
Ukraine, subscribe
Україні підпишись